Guide to the Records of John Brademas Speeches 1965-1991 RG 3.0.10 RG 3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Alumni Commencement Breakfast, NYU, (JB Greetings), Jun 5, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - NYU Commencement & Trustee Dinner/Tisch remarks, NYU, (Greetings), Jun 5, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - 155th NYU Commencement, NYU, (Honorary Degrees to: Avery Fisher, Philip Johnson, Amalya Kyle Kearse, Torsten Nils Wiesel, Claiborne Pell), Jun 5, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - BPA Entrepreneur of the Year Award Dinner, NYC, (John Catsimatidis, Contributions of NYU to Entrepreneurship), Jun 6, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Hospitality Industry, NYC, (Hotel Industry), Jun 9, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Abraham Gitlow Chair in Business Administration, NYU, (Importance of Endowed Professorships), Jun 10, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - University of Athens, Athens, (Acceptance of Honorary Degree), Jun 12, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Sackler Wing at Met, NYC, (Saekler), Jun 17, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Ecumenical Doxology Homily, NYC, (Archbishop Iakoavos Anniversary), Jul 4, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Atlantic Institute, Paris, ("Congress & American Foreign Policy: The Lessons of Irangate), Jul 6, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner, Indianapolis, (Intro. of Cuomo), Jul 28, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - American Scientist Article, (Science), Jul 30, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Tribute/Joseph E. Levine, NYC, (Joseph E. Levine), Aug 3, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Encyclopedia of NYC Endorsement, NYC, (Endorsement), Aug 14, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Article for PS Magazine, (Fulbright Distinguished Fellows), Aug 31, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Student Convocation, NYU, (Greetings), Sep 14, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Inauguration at Jewish Theological Seminary,NYU, (Greetings), Sep 14, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Panel Discussion/Center for Strategic & Int'l Studies, Washington, DC, (Bicentennial of Constitution), Sep 15, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - National Council of Jewish Women, NYC, (The Role of Congress in American Foreign Policy), Sep 17, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Clark Convocation, Worchester, (Higher Education), Sep 18, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Society of Park & Recreation Educators, New Orleans, (Leisure), Sep 20, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Welcome Back Party, NYU, (JB Greetings to NYU Administrators), Sep 21, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - NYU Board of Trustees, NYU, (NYU Affairs), Sep 21, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Doxology at Greek Orthodox Archdiocesan Cathedral Holy Trinity, Greek Orthodox Cathedral, (Greek Heritage, U.S. Constitution), Sep 27, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Wu Xueqian Luncheon, Pratt House Council on Foreign Relations, (Welcoming Remarks), Sep 29, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Orzechowski Luncheon, Bobst-Conf. Rm. (Improving U.S.-Polish Foreign Relations, Etc.), Sep 30, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Methodist Blurb, Bobst, (Script for Methodist TV Taping), Oct 6, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Medical Center Board Remarks, Medical Science Bldg, (Address to Medical Center Board), Oct 6, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Reception for New Graduate Students, Loeb-Eisner & Lubin, (Welcome to Students, Talk about NYU), Oct 6, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Haskins Award Dinner, Hotel Pierre, (Brief Talk About BPA & W. Michael Blumenthal), Oct 7, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Group Portrait, (Introduction to S. Groennings Book), Oct 7, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - New York Observer Article, NY Observer Newspaper, (Importance of NYU to Manhattan), Oct 13, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Iona College Fall Honors Convocation, Iona College, (Role of Congress in American Foreign Policy: Bicentennial Perspective), Oct 18, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - GBA Overseers' Dinner, Bobst-Snow, (Toast to H. Kaufman, & Fundraising Report), Oct 19, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Breakfast for NYU Orientation Leaders, Bobst-Ben Snow, (To Honor Student Orientation Leaders), Oct 19, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Board of Trustees Remarks, Bobst-Conf. Rm., (Report on Status of NYU), Oct 19, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Join Leaders of America Alumni Breakfast, Regency Hotel Grand Ballroom, (To Kick-off New Alumni Unrestricted Campaign), Oct 20, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - American Antiquarian Society, Mechanics Hall- Worchester, MA, (Speech on Learned Societies, Etc.), Oct 21, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - All University Convocation, Loeb/Eisner & Lubin Auditorium, (Tribute to Outstanding NYU Professors), Oct 22, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - NYS School Boards Assoc. Annual Convention Speech, Empire State Plaza Conven.Center, (Talk on Education, Public Schools), Oct 23, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Associates Annual Awards Dinner, Whitney Museum, (Addressing Phi Beta on NYU), Oct 24, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - FAS Newsletter, (JB Ushers in New Era for NYU), Oct 27, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - National Broadcasting Seminar, Bobst, (Talking Points For Month-Long Program for Int'l Broadcasters), Oct 27, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - GBA Annual Awards Dinner, World Trade Center, (Tribute to Accomplishments of Teachers, Graduates), Oct 27, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - 40th Anniversary: Institute of Environmental Medicine, NYU Med Ctr, (Celebration of Founding of Environmental Medicine), Oct 29, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Carnegie Council Ethics & International Affairs, 170 E. 64th St., (Role of Congress in American Foreign Policy: Bicentennial Perspective), Oct 30, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Metro Center Press Conference, Bobst, (NYU Metro Center Receiving $3.2 million from U.S. Dept of Education), Nov 2, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Metro Center Press Conference, Bobst, (NYU Metro Center Receiving 3.2 Million from U.S. Dept. of Education), Nov 2, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - University Senate, Bobst, (JB Report), Nov 12, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Fed. of State Humanities Councils, Chicago, IL (Arts & Public Policy), Nov 14, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Trustees Scholar Dinner, Bobst, (JB Remarks), Nov 19, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Assoc. for Higher Education, Baltimore, MD, (Keynote Address), Nov 22, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - Harvard Education Seminar, (Politics of Ed.), Nov 23, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - Memo to 41st Pres. of U.S., Various, (Emphasis on Education), Dec 1987 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - Fourth Estate Dinner Talking Points, Dec 2, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - The Century Association, Century Club, (Monthly Meeting of Club), Dec 3, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - Exec. Comm. of Med. Ctr. Board, Medical Ctr., (Report to Med. Ctr. Board), Dec 3, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Board of Trustees, Bobst, (JB Report), Dec 7, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - SCE M.S. in Real Estate, Midtown Ctr,. (Formal Announcement), Dec 7, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 102)
  - Dinner at Isabel Leeds/Spain, Leeds House, (Personal Reflections), Dec 8, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 103)
  - UJA Dinner for Arthur L. Linman, Sheraton, NY, (Proskauer Award Dinner), Dec 9, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - President's Council Reception, Penthouse, (Talk to NYU Supporters), Dec 10, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Billington Lecture, Great Hall, (Intro of J. Billington), Dec 10, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 106)
  - NEA/SEHNAP Press Luncheon,Bobst ,(NEA Establishment at NYU), Dec 14, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Luncheon for Librarians, Bobst, (Libraries Convocation), Dec 15, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Libraries Dinner Remarks, Bobst, (Libraries Convocation), Dec 15, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Mrs. Bobst's Remraks, Bobst, (Libraries Convocation), Dec 15, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Libraries Convocation, Bobst, (In Praise of Libraries & Etc.), Dec 15, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Libraries Script & Instructions, Bobst, (In Praise of Libraries & Etc.), Dec 15, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Education Week Commentary, Wash., DC, (Education Commentary), Dec 15, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Faculty Council, Bobst, (Report to Faculty Council), Dec 17, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Aspen Institute Speech, Berlin, Germany, (The World, America, Congress), Jan 12, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254691
  - Redlich Tribute - NYU Law Review, NYU Law Review, (Norman Redlich), Jan 12, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Royal Inst. of Int'l Affairs, London, England, (The American System of Gov't), Jan 14, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Chief Academic Officers Photo Exh., Bobst Conf. Rm., (Brief Remarks of Welcome), Jan 20, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Talking Points IFA Board Mtg., 1 E. 78th St., (NYU News), Jan 22, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Conf. on Teaching of Ethics, Ann Harbor, MI (Education, The World), Jan 29, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Cong. Competitiveness Caucus, Wash., DC, (Higher Education), Feb 2, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - ACCU Speech - Role of Higher Ed., Palm Beach, FL, (Higher Education), Feb 2, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Palm Beach I - Social Events, Palm Beach, FL, (NYU), Feb 4, 1988-Feb 7, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Luncheon Seminar David Butler, NYU, (Talking Points), Mar 18, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - NYU in Albany Talking Points, Albany, NY, (Talking Points in Albany), Mar 22, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Eli Evans Reception, Pres. Conf. Rm., (Thank You & Remarks), Mar 21, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Nat'1 Academy of Arts & Sci. Dinner, Bobst, (Remarks to AAAS Group), Mar 23, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, (Talking Points), Mar 23, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Nat'l Comm. on Amer. Foreign Policy, Lotos Club, (Foreign Policy), Mar 29, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Phila. Alumni Reception, Hershey Hotel, (Standard Alumni Speech to NYU Graduates), Mar 30, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies Press Conference, Pres. Conf. Rm., (Remarks for Press Conference), Mar 30, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Metro Center Luncheon, Waldorf Astoria, (Awarding of Torch of Learning), Mar 31, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Ditchley Foundations Conference, England, (Terms of Reference Paper), Apr 1988-Oct 1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Wash. Sq. Park Clean-Up, Wash. Sq. Pk., (Brief Thank Yous to City Officials), Apr 5, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Report of Pres. to Med. Ctr. Board, Med. Sci. Bldg., (Update on Square Developments), Apr 5, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - NYU/Spanish Inst. Book Party, Bobst, Conf. Rm,. (Welcoming Remarks to Prof. Albornoz), Apr 6, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Down Town Association, 60 Pine Street, (Wash., DC to Wash.,Square), Apr 20, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees Report, Bobst, (Report on Current Developments), Apr 20, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Congressional Arts Caucus Luncheon, TSOA, Bobst, (Talking Points), Apr 22, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Founders Day Address, Coles Sport Ctr., (1988 Founders Day Convocation), Apr 24, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Dinner for Sir Peter Ramsbotham, Bobst, Conf. Rm., (Talking Points for Dinner), Apr 25, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Humanities Coun. Peter Ramsbotham, Tisch Hall, (Intro. of Sir Peter Ramsbotham), Apr 25, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Council on Economic Priorities, 30 Irving Pl., (Brief Remarks), Apr 26, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - NYU Law & Philanthropy Grant, Bobst, Conf. Rm, (Luncheon Honoring New NYU Law School in Law & Philanthrophy Grant), Apr 27, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - David Kriser Dinner, Harmonie Club, (Family of NYU Kriser Tribute), Apr 27, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Mel Miller Dinner, (Talking points), Apr 28, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - CASH Luncheon Briefing, Bobst Conf. Rm., (Memo of Points to Refer To), Apr 28, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - The James Family & Italy, Tishman Aud,.( Welcoming Remarks), Apr 29, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - NYU Spring Celebration, Coles, (State of NYU), Apr 29, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Univ. of Charleston Commencement, C. W. VA., (Commencement Remarks), May 1, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Higher Education Seminar, D'Agostino Hall, ( Talk Based on Pol of Ed.), May 2, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Tribute to Juge Weinfeld, School of Law, (Tribute to Weinfeld), May 2, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - New York Federal Executive Board, One Federal Plz,.( Value of Public Service), May 2, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - SEHNAP Prism Award, Windows on World, (Brief Remarks on SEHNAP'S GCMT), May 2, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Real Estate Institute Breakfast, NYU Midtown, (Remarks for New Master of Science Fundraiser), May 3, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - IFA Board Meeting, IFA, (Talking Points for the Last IFA Mtg.), May 4, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Education Daily Consensus Panel To Joe McGavin, (Ed. Daily Article), May 1988 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo, Bobst, (JB Remarks), May 9, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - NYU Board of Trustees, Bobst Library, (Report to Trustees), May 9, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Visiting Mayors Urban Research Ctr., D'Agostino Hall, (Welcome, Introductions), May 12, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - University Senate Report, Bobst Library, (Progress Report), May 12, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Sweeney Scholarship Program Luncheon, Pres. Conf. Rm., (Sweeney Program), May 16, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - 25 Year Service Awards, Loeb, TOP, (Brief Remarks Award Pres.), May 17, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Dutch Treat Club Lunch, Sardi's, (NYU and New York City), May 17, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Alumni Council Dinner, D'Agostino Hall, (General & Brief Remarks), May 17, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - CREO Society Penthouse Concert, Sun Room, (Talking Points), May 18, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - "Le Cirque" Luncheon, Le Cirque Rest. (French Bicent. Remarks), May 18, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - NYU Community Fund, NYU, (Talking Points), May 19, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - South Bend Boosters Hall of Fame, Notre Dame, IN (Acceptance Remarks), May 21, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson Uni. Commencement, Byrne Arena, (Commencement Remarks), May 22, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Farewell to Dean Redlich, Harmonie Club, (Farewell to Dean Redlich), May 31, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Benaki Museum Intro, NYU, (Greek Exhibition), Jun 1988 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Lunch Honoring Guggenheim Fellows, Bobst, (JB Brief Remarks), Jun 1, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Remarks & Script for Commencement, Bobst, (Honorees: Edward Finkelstein, Hanna Gray, Max Kampelman, Charles Rangel, Martin Segal), Jun 2, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, Bobst, (Honorary Degree Recipients), Jun 2, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting, NYU, (Report of the President-NYU), Jun 10, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Reception for Dean Howard Newman, Bobst, (Dean Newman), Jun 15, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Greek Orthodox Archdoicese, Boston, MA, (JB Receives Award), Jul 6, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Education Daily Consensus Panel, NYU, (College Athletics), Jul 7, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Reception Washington Workshops, Tisch, (JB Greeting), Jul 10, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Blurb for the Vulnerable, NYU, Jul 13, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Blurb for Merch & Company, NYU, (Address to Sigma Xi), Jul 13, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Welcoming M. Cuomo, M. Dukakis, Loeb, (Introduction), Aug 11, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Metro Center Upward Bound, NYU-Snow Dining, (Upward Bound Lunch & Graduation), Aug 12, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - NEXUS Article on Science, NYU, (Ltr to Kenneth Jon Rose), Aug 12, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Intro - Political Science Book, NYU, Aug 14, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Intro - How to Succeed in Business, NYU, (Summer Musical Theatre), Aug 14, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Notes on Leadership, NYU, (Leaders), Aug 14, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Liberal Education Essay, NYU, (Liberal Arts), Aug 17, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Bronx Higher Education, Lehman College, (Student Aid), Aug 23, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Letter to Dukakis, (Comments "Mike Dukakis on the Issues: College Opport.", Aug 25, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Letter to Janet Kerr-Tener, Ph.D., (Presidency & Education), Aug 25, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - NYU Magazine, (Letter for the President), Aug 30, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Dedication of Sidney & Sarah Brown Study Center, Vanderbilt Hall, (Dedication of New Study Center in the Law Library), Aug 30, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - School of Law Faculty Luncheon, Great Hall, (Welcoming Back Faculty), Sep 1, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Foreword-The Presidency in American Politics, Sep 1, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Student Convocation, Loeb, (Welcoming of New Undergraduate Students), Sep 6, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Statement in Support of Dukakis, (JB Statement), Sep 7, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Board of Regents, NYU, (Talking Points), Sep 8, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - Jill Krementz's Manuscript, (Review of Krementz's Ms.), Sep 12, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Dr. Stratigos' Document, (Review of Stratigo's Document), Sep 12, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Letter to Harold Brown, (Congress & Foreign Policy), Sep 19, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - NYU Board of Trustees, Bobst, (Report to Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees), Sep 19, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Response to George Bull, (Suggested Response to Bull), Sep 20, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - University Senate, NYU, (Report to Univ. Senate), Sep 22, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Harold Weill Medal Presentation Dinner, D'Agostino Hall (Presentation of Weill Medal), Sep 26, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Reception for New Graduate Students, Loeb, (JB Remarks to Grad Students), Sep 27, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Mitterrand Convocation/Dinner, NYU-Bobst, (JB & Tisch Remarks/Toast for Dinner), Sep 28, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Women's Campaign Fund Dinner, NYC (Talking Points/Background Info), Sep 29, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Briefing for Rhodes Scholar, NYU, (Making the U.S. Government More Effective), Sep 30, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - GBA Conference on Japan/US Relations, NYU, (Japanese/US Relations in the Post-Reagan Era), Oct 3, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Beta Gamma Sigma Alumni, NYU Club, (Education & The Nation's Agenda: Perspectives in an Election Year), Oct 3, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Charles Waldo Haskins Dinner, Pierre Hotel, (Annual Dinner, Honoring Peter G. Peterson), Oct 4, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Leonard N. Stern School of Business Press Conference, Bobst, (Remarks at Press Conference Announcing Naming of School), Oct 6, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - American Council for the Arts. Conf., New Brunswick, NJ, (Address '88 National Arts Convention of the ACA), Oct 7, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Medical Center Board Remarks, NYU, (Report to Medical Center Board), Oct 7, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Special Celebration/Dinner in Honor Georgakis & Vryonis, Tishman Aud. (Jb Libretto & Remarks/Dinner Remarks), Oct 10, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Stern School of Business Board of Overseers Dinner, Bobst, (JB Brief Remarks), Oct 18, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Art & Business Council Luncheon, Waldorf-Astoria, (24th Annual Encore Awards Honoring Joseph Papp), Oct 20, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Reception for Martin Luther King Scholars, Bobst, (Honroing NYU MLK Scholars), Oct 20, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - All-University Convocation, Loeb, (JB Remarks), Oct 20, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Annual Archbishop Lakovos Feastday Dinner, D.C., (Libretto & Remarks for Dinner), Oct 22, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Penthouse Dinner for GPA Dean Newman, Penthouse, (Remarks & Dinner for Newman), Oct 24, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Campaign for Oxford Convocation, Oxford England, (JB Remarks), Oct 26, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254741
  - National Arts Club Dinner, Nation Arts Club, (Honoring William Passannante), Oct 26, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Allen Bloom Rebuttal, (Rebutting Bloom), Oct 28, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Education for a Strong & Secure America: An Election-Eve Persp., D.C., (Remarks before the Woman's National Democratic Club), Oct 31, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Post Election Thoughts on the New President & Educ., Nov 8, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - University Senate, NYU, (Report to Univ. Senate), Nov 10, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts & Letters, Bobst, (Honorees: Edward Albee, Robert Giroux, Toni Morrison, and Reynolds Price), Nov 14, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - NYU Opportunity Fellows Reception, Bobst, (Honoring NYU Opport. Fellows), Nov 14, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 1st Liberty Forum Luncheon, Sheraton Centre, (MC for Luncheon Sponsored by Williamsburg Charter Found.), Nov 15, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Education Daily Consensus Panel, (Response of JB), Nov 15, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Trustees Scholars Dinner, Ben Snow/Pres., (Honoring Trustees Scholars), Nov 16, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Los Angeles Alumni Reception, Beverly Hills, (Informal Report on the Univer.), Nov 21, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 1988 Axios Man of the Year Award, Beverly Hills, (JB Receives Axios Award), Nov 22, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Economic Dev. Inst. of the World Bank Seminar on Quality & Efficiency of Higher Education, Brasilia, ( Excellence & Opportunity:Challenge to the Modern Univ.), Nov 27, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 10th Anniversary Hubert Humphrey Fellowship Speech in Brazil, Rio De Janeiro, (The Vision of H. Humphrey: Education for a Better Tomorrow), Dec 1, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - America in Theory Reception, Bobst, (Book Party to Celebrate Publication), Dec 5, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Service Reception, Bobst, (Honoring NYU Faculty, 10, 15, 20 and 25 Years of Service), Dec 5, 1988-12/7/1988 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Intro to Dan Rostenkowski/Tax Conference Dinner, World Trade Ctr., (Conference on Taxation), Dec 6, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Medical Center Board, NYU, (Report to Executive Committee), Dec 6, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - University Senate, Bobst, (Report to University Senate), Dec 8, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Arthur L. Carter Hall Dedication, Carter Hall, (Dedication Ceremonies), Dec 12, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Board of Trustees, NYU, (Report to Full Board), Dec 12, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Stern Dinner, Bobst, (Honoring Mr. & Mrs. Stern), Dec 13, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Speros Vryonis Lecture, NY Public Lib., (Marking 900th Anniversary of St. John Monastery, Patmos, Greece), Dec 13, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Jt. Economic Committee Testimony, Washington, DC, (Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on Education & Health), Dec 14, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon, NYU, (Report to Full Faculty Coun.), Dec 15, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Issues in the 101st Congress, NYU, (Reaction to ACE document), Dec 21, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Politics of Education, (Reaction and PR), Dec 21, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Father Rafferty Farewell, Catholic Center, (Ltr. from JB Bidding Farewell), Jan 11, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - American Council on Education, San Diego, CA, (JB Remarks at '89 Annual Mtg.), Jan 20, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Eagleton Response to Harold Brown Document, (Congress & Foreign Policy), Jan 20, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Medical Center Press Conference, Univ. Hosp,.(Announcing Gift from Tisches), Jan 25, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - NYU Alumni Reception in Atlanta, Atlanta, GA, (JB Remarks), Jan 27, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - IFA Board Meeting, Bobst, (JB Talking Points), Jan 30, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies Dinner, Bobst, (Report on Development at the Onassis Center), Jan 30, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Committee of the Year 2000 Meeting, The Regency, (JB remarks), Jan 31, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - An Olive Branch Within Easy Reach, (Essay), Feb 1989 (Box 13, Folder 37)